{
    "id": "2d5689d476654f2386a7c804366e2fb3",
    "title": "Adjectives Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "There I met a very beautiful woman.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "met",
                "very",
                "beautiful"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c6a14e4825414bfe9c0c94253a898b68"
        },
        {
            "question": "The kind hostess made sure that everyone was happy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "sure",
                "everyone",
                "happy"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "503069f7b02f47008db9762488d94d4a"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was wearing a red shirt.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "red",
                "shirt"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "809089ccffc649c49917573390cab784"
        },
        {
            "question": "The rich woman is known for her generosity.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "rich",
                "known",
                "generosity"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f97d3006f30a4bda90d1d3725d15bc60"
        },
        {
            "question": "In spite of being rich and famous, she leads a miserable life.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "In spite of",
                "famous",
                "rich"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "12a8a537007e48ccb320f6a0aa4ba41a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Her arrogant nature made her very unpopular.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "arrogant",
                "nature",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7300bac62f144d939f6adbc61dfcee46"
        },
        {
            "question": "He wants to be a successful lawyer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "he",
                "successful",
                "lawyer"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "48fb79d0ecad48ce9f6542753a63d339"
        },
        {
            "question": "The anxious mother waited for a call from her son.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "anxious",
                "mother",
                "call"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4ecb5391976445f289d714d469dda45f"
        },
        {
            "question": "The old man has seen better days.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "old",
                "man",
                "days"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "66c7d04fc15a4ed4a05b4eee69e51f93"
        },
        {
            "question": "Iron is a useful metal.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "iron",
                "useful",
                "metal"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a10b33c41daf4fa2a513ba500215cd62"
        },
        {
            "question": "The offer was so good that I could not refuse it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "offer",
                "so",
                "good"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c98c27310b95435caa12d7723a1b265b"
        }
    ]
}